Hello? I think you can hear me.
Let's hope we're coming through
clear. I wanted to share
about the idea of old reminders.
And by that I mean things coming up
that at one
time were either persistent or you
know multiple times a day kind of
things.
And it's after you've had some time
with those things not present in
your life for a while they
can show their ugly heads once
again. Which is unfortunate but it
is what it is. So...
I had been feeling great. Well, my
version of great is someone's
really down day. But that is
shifting and I'm glad for that.
And so the shift for me or let's
say there were, excuse me, let's
start over one more fucking time.
Yeah, so the reminder in my case
was not about a thing. No. Because
I could insert any
focus or point of focus into this.
What it is is a behavior. And the
behavior being something
in the abstract would go something
like this. You are going about your
day. You know you may have a game
plan. Shit you want to get done.
Or it could be a carefree laissez-
faire day. You know and things just
roll how they roll.
This was a, I got a list 35 fucking
feet long and I need to get some
shit done.
So when this behavior shows up,
number one it's annoying in and of
itself. The behavior. Number
two then there's the focus of
whatever the behavior is focused
on. Then if you're a lucky
chap like myself, you have the
metacognitive ability to float your
brain outside of this
whole scenario. And watch yourself
get fucked over by yourself is
basically what I'm talking about.
And it's, I just realized it's
pretty awful that I'm laughing. But
I've lived so many